Folio Society Collection
Folio Society Collection
- Unidentified publications
  - [unnumbered] Tristram Shandy / Laurence Sterne, 1953; 1956 (Box 2)
Grant, AlistairFS 80
Greenaway, George W.FS 152
Grimsditch, Herbert B.FS 113
Hampden, JohnFS 193 FS 194 FS 209
Harris, DerrickFS 56 FS 78 FS 128 FS 0
Harris, MargaretFS 173
Hart, KingsleyFS 136
Hartz, SamFS 47
Hassall, JoanFS 17 FS 37 FS 122 FS 135 FS 147 FS 157 FS 175 FS 189
Hawthorn, RaymondFS 116 FS 127 FS 164 FS 192
Hogarth, PaulFS 115 FS 144
Holland, VyvyanFS 63
Hopkins, GerardFS 130
Hopkins, KennethFS 197
Hough, GrahamFS 184
Hughes-Stanton, BlairFS 6
Hugo, JeanFS 27
Hurry, LeslieFS 154
Jennings, ElizabethFS 160
Jordan, K.C.FS 156
Jullian, PhilippeFS 180
Keeling, CecilFS 143
Ketton-Cremer, R.W.FS 35
Lachouque, HenryFS 104
Lamb, LyntonFS 15 FS 88 FS 182
Lambourne, NigelFS 65 FS 130 FS 155 FS 194
Lancaster, OsbertFS 188
Lawrence, JohnFS 236
Le Campion, ValentinFS 29
Lewis, OscarFS 133
Lewis, Wilmarth S.FS 35
Liddell Hart, B.H.FS 156
Lloyd, ChristopherFS 165
Lockyer, RogerFS 125
Lucas, F.L.FS 11 FS 26
Martin, FrankFS 89 FS 124 FS 153 FS 207
Magarshack, DavidFS 194
Masterman, DodieFS 84 FS 213
Meiggs, RussellFS 127
Moiseiwitsch, TanyaFS 81
Neama, MayFS 142
Nicolson, HaroldFS 36
Olivier, Sir LaurenceFS 13 FS 46 FS 71
Palmer, GarrickFS 232
Parker, Geoffrey H.W.FS 178
Peake, MervynFS 12
Phelps, GilbertFS 171
Piper, JohnFS 172
Read, H. HopeFS 10
Reddick, PeterFS 197
Ribbons, IanFS 103
Richardson, Sir RalphFS 105
Rieser, DolfFS 50
Rogers, PaulFS 129
Roseman, LeonardFS 119
Ross, Philip E.FS 91
Rossem, Ru vanFS 24 FS 31 FS 57 FS 101
Sackville-West, EdwardFS 29
Sadleir, MichaelFS 2
Sala Grau, JoanFS 44
Scofield, PaulFS 118
Scott, W. SidneyFS 45 FS 172
Seale, DouglasFS 154
Selver, PaulFS 170
Severin, MarkFS 117
Sharp, RichardFS 58
Shaw, Glen ByamFS 173
Stone, AlixFS 199
Stone, ReynoldsFS 4 FS 169 FS 0
Sutcliffe, BerkeleyFS 129
Svolinsky, KarelFS 170
Tree, Herbert BeerbohmFS 2
Vertes, MarcelFS 96
Wain, JohnFS 161
Wales, GeoffreyFS 64
Wedgwood, Cicely VeronicaFS 125 FS 195
Welles, OrsonFS 81
Wetherbee, MargaretFS 43
Whyte, EdnaFS 98, 100
Williams, EmlynFS 62
Wolfit, DonaldFS 93